One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
Don't pretend you can't see it.
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
We haven't even started yet!
I wanna know it all! Now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can! This moment...
We can! I can! With this feeling of freedom...
Now... Now, oh yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
Raizo of the Mist
We have a problem! Kin'emon and Kanjurou must've arrived already!
Because of some samurai named Raizo who isn't even here, the Mokomo Dukedom was destroyed!
If they meet the Minks and say they're looking for Raizo,
it's gonna be messy!
Anyway, we have to stop those two!
Yeah!
Let's go!
This is serious-saru! This is serious-saru!
Bariete's ringing the bell!
Samurai-saru!
Samurai are here-saru!
Let's go to the city!
Tell everyone who is capable to follow me!
Yes, sir!
Duke-sama! Your Warney is ready!
By the way, that bell is very noisy.
It's been ringing constantly.
Isn't it a bell to tell everyone they have a visitor?
They must be welcoming us!
That's certainly possible!
But Law-dono was saying that...
...the inhabitants of Zou who don't like humans
are actually the Mink Tribe.
Yes, is that what people are saying?
I can't understand why.
If that's what people are saying these days...
Father! Kanjurou!
Momonosuke!
Kanjurou! So you're all right!
Ah, I'm sorry to make you worry.
Now, why are you here alone?
Where are Luffy-dono and everybody?
Actually, I haven't been at ease
since we came to this country
so I've been sleeping in a room by myself.
Oh no!
You poor thing.
I see. Then come with us.
I guess they're assembling to welcome us!
Why?! Why?! Why?!
Why should I be running this early in the morning?!
I told you! Kin'emon and...
What was his name?!
Kanjurou!
Yes! Those two arrived!
They say two samurai appeared
and the whole country is in a great uproar!
Master Nekomamushi headed for the city
leading the Guardians!
Another welcome banquet?!
I wouldn't mind having one for two consecutive days!
No, they've got a score to settle!
Of course, they do!
They were wrongly accused of hiding a samurai
and almost died!
Where are they?!
We'll find them right away!
People across the country
keep rolling into the city...
Pedro! Can you see them?!
This is no good.
Can't you find the samurai yet?!
We're on the hunt now!
Master, please pull back!
Pull back?!
Hurry up!
Humph! What are you talking about?!
Please. Just keep going.
Oh... Oh no! The two ran into each other!
Master!
Duke-sama!
Please don't do it, Master!
Duke-sama! Please calm down!
Is it a fight?
That's...
Man! That was...
...Really close!
You three, take my advice
and go back to the Sunny now!
How many years has it been, cat monster?
You've become even more monstrous.
What about you-gara?
You've lost one of your legs.
What should we do?!
Somebody, please stop them!
Where is Raizo?!
Give us Raizo!
I know Raizo is in this country!
We don't have such a person here!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Search through the country as you please!
We don't have a samurai...
I wonder if you'll say goodbye to this leg first,
or tell us where the samurai is.
Let's try it, "Dog King."
Then, there is no way
for me to save this leg.
You-gara got your hand chopped off.
You can't fight anymore.
The most you can do is eat lasagna.
Say it! Where's the samurai?!
How can I tell you something I don't know?!
A person from the Land of
Wano has no business here!
All you can do is use poison gas
and attack the weakened men!
You cowards!
Oh no! This guy's trying to break the chains!
Is the gas really working?!
Immobilize his arms!
Yeah, you'd better do that!
If you have time to harm my people,
point your spear at me!
No... Master!
I'll take all of those crappy spears myself!
Master!
It's a shame that
you-gara have only lost one of your legs!
I wouldn't mind if you were dead.
One king is enough for the country!
Please stop, both of you!
Then let's send one of us to kingdom come!
You-gara must die!
A dog and a cat?!
Hey!
I heard about it before,
but they're really strong!
Hey, wait!
Stop fighting!
Hey, you idiot! What are you doing?!
That's...
...a samurai!
See?! They found you!
Run, Kin'emon! They're gonna kill you!
Momo-chan!
Hey, let go of me! Please!
What are you gonna do?!
Momo, stay away!
Kanjurou! Why did you guys come out?!
Run! Now!
Nekomamushi! Inuarashi! Wait a minute!
They really mean no harm!
People from the country of Zou!
I'm a retainer of the Kozuki Clan from
the Land of Wano, named Kin'emon!
I'm here to look for my comrade named Raizo who is a warrior from the same country!
Has he been here?!
Well, this country was destroyed
because he wasn't here!
Luffy!
Yeah...
We've been expecting you.
I don't know Raizo! I swear to god!
If the man you're talking about is here,
you can take my life!
Raizo-dono is...
...safe!
Oh, he's safe! I'm relieved!
Whoa, wait a minute!
Hey, was Raizo here all this time?!
Did you all know?!
Y-Y-Y-You all almost died!
The millennium-old city was ruined!
I'm sorry that we kept it a secret
from you-gara guys too.
The Land of Wano's Kozuki Clan
and we have been like a family since way back.
No matter what will be ruined,
we'd never sell out our friends!
Hey!
Yes, sir!
What do you think? Am I dead?
N-No! Definitely not!
You're alive, Jack-sama!
I'm deeply grateful to you all!
And now, as proof, I offer you this!
Yes, that's certainly the same Kozuki Clan crest that Duke-sama, Master and Raizo-san have!
Kozuki...
I can't believe they know each other!
I was really prepared for a
clash against the Minks! Jeez!
It couldn't be helped.
They couldn't have told the whole story even to us.
She just said the doggy and the kitty
have the same crest.
Maybe, their bond is far
stronger than we realize.
But Inuarashi, Nekomamushi...
It is surprising to see you two
alive and well here!
Death would've been a relief to us.
But we thought if we trust the words
from that day and wait here...
Yeah, then we would get
to see you-gara guys one day!
Hey, cat monster!
I was talking to Kin'emon!
Don't interrupt as you please!
I was just thinking Kin'emon must be
sick of talking to you-gara
so I tactfully took over!
I thought they were cooled down.
Well...
You-gara served your purpose! Get lost!
You get lost!
Please stop, both of you!
Our long-awaited guests have just arrived!
Stop fighting! Inuarashi! Nekomamushi!
You two used to be such good friends! Why have you been fighting like you wanna kill each other?!
Well...
I forbid you to ever fight again!
It's even more inexcusable
if it's because of my father!
It would make my father sad
to see you two like this...
Oden-sama...
Momo?
Did you say it'd make your father sad?
But Kin'emon's right here.
I'm sorry!
Momonosuke-sama! I'm ashamed of myself!
You're absolutely right!
What?!
Duke-sama!
I can't believe Master's bowing his head!
Would that child be...
Momonosuke-sama is right!
Please forgive me for lying to you all, too!
To tell you the truth, Momonosuke-sama and I are...
...not father and son!
What?!
This man right here is the heir to...
...Kozuki Oden-sama, great daimyo of Kuri in the Land of Wano!
Kingdom of Wano
Heir of the Daimyo of Kuri
Kozuki Momonosuke
His name is Kozuki Momonosuke-sama!
That means for all of us including
Inuarashi and Nekomamushi,
he's our lord!
So he's the heir of the Kozuki Family
and Oden-dono's son!
How could I miss that?!
What? Is Momo someone important?
If they're heading the list of his retainers,
he could be quite a powerful lord.
Along the way, if his true identity was revealed,
we could've attracted more enemies
so we pretended as if we were father and son.
Although we trusted you all,
we never had a good chance to tell you.
I apologize.
So you're not father and son.
But they're alike. They're both perverts.
I'm sorry that I was lying!
I'm actually an important figure!
Yes, and a pervert.
No, I'm not!
Whatever!
What do you mean by that?!
Bow down, Luffy!
No way!
Why do we have to change our behavior just because you're an important person?! Idiot!
M-Momonosuke-sama!
You're afraid of heights
and you have no guts!
We samurai aren't afraid of anything!
How rude!
Here we go again.
He saved our lives but...
You can't ask a pirate to be humble.
Momonosuke-sama's getting
distracted, so that's good.
So frustrating, Onami!
Luffy is a terrible guy!
Oh, there, there.
Stay away from her, Momonosuke-sama!
You damn brat!
Hey!
Say, Momo-chan,
if your father is a lord, there must be
treasure in his castle, isn't that right?
Cut it out!
You're really a bad person!
It's only been a few months since...
Their-gara cheeriness must be helping him.
Let's make a truce, cat.
If we keep dwelling in the past,
we'll make Momonosuke-sama suffer.
Okay, for the sake of our lord!
I'll communicate with you-gara
but won't connect with you-gara!
That's a deal!
Oh! Look at that!
Those two are... No way!
It's a miracle!
Our two kings made up!
The King of the Day and the King of the Night finally...
How amazing the Kozuki Family's power is!
It makes me cry!
Dr. Miyagi! You're hopping too much!
Let's climb the whale.
If you learn which vines to take,
you can reach the top.
So Raizo's here?!
Nin-nin!
Can't wait to see the ninja! Nin-nin!
I get to see a ninja! Nin-nin!
The Watery Escape Technique! Nin-nin!
I still don't feel well, Kin'emon.
You can wait at the bottom if you want,
Momonosuke-sama.
As we get closer to the whale,
the voice I hear is getting louder.
You have a similar ability to Oden-sama.
There was another man
who used to say something like that.
I was just thinking about the same thing.
Oh, I can't believe there's an entrance here!
On the tail of the Whale Tree?!
No one would notice!
And it's a hidden door
so it's impossible to find.
Let's go.
It's a long flight of stairs so be careful.
Is that...
That's Raizo's voice.
What?! The ninja?!
Ninja!
Where's the ninja?!
Ninja! Ninja!
Here we are.
He-gara is the ninja, Raizo.
Ninja! Nin...
There you are, Nekomamushi!
You! Why didn't you just hand me over to them?!
Ninja from the Kingdom of Wano
Raizo of the Mist
Everyone that brought me food here...
...was injured!
They told me the country is okay,
but is it true?!
If it's a lie, I, Raizo, will hate you!
What?!
He's nothing like we expected!
I don't think you guys are from this country!
Who are you?!
Raizo!
Kin'emon! Kanjuro! Momonosuke-sama!
I'm glad that you're okay!
We're glad you're okay too!
That's...
The crest of the Kozuki Family!
The same as Kin'emon's!
That crest has existed for centuries.
And that stone is...
I've never seen it in such a color.
Deep red...
Yeah, it's a Poneglyph.
We know you-gara, Nico Robin.
I heard the Ohara people
can read those letters.
Why is that Poneglyph red?
None of the Poneglyphs I've ever seen
were that color.
It has a different purpose.
Can you read it?
Yes, may I?
Of course, you may.
What's wrong with you guys?
Why are you staring hard at me like that?
Are you really a ninja?
How insolent! Who are you?!
We haven't introduced them to you yet.
Raizo, they're the Straw Hats.
They're pirates.
Pirates?
If you're a real ninja, throw a shuriken!
Meditate under a waterfall!
Say "Nin" and use ninja powers!
I wanna see the Earth Escape Technique!
I want the fire version!
No, the water version!
Such rapid-fire requests!
Why do you pirates want to see it so badly?!
It's not because we're pirates.
Super!
All boys like ninjas!
That makes me blush.
Hey, have you ever gone out
with a female ninja?!
Train your jumping ability
by jumping over a bamboo shoot every day!
Show me the Shadow Clone Technique.
Hide in the ceiling and
get stabbed by a spear.
Summon a giant frog!
Hold a scroll in your
mouth and say "Nin-nin"!
Oh, shut up!
Stop imposing your damn dreams on me!
We ninja don't say things like "Nin-nin"!
The ninja in your heads are all fantasies!
What?!
Then, what makes you a ninja?!
It can't be your physique!
That's right. With this physique,
I can't even attract female ninjas...
Hey, shut up!
Listen! It takes a quiet and
tough mind to be a master ninja!
We're supposed to be living in the shadows.
We can't show off our techniques.
Ninjutsu is not entertainment...
Ninpo - Smoke Escape Technique!
He disappeared!
I didn't disappear!
I'm here.
Wh-What?!
And here!
Here too!
And here too!
What?! He's got doubles?!
Could it be...?!
Ninpo - Shadow Clone Technique!
Cool!
Did you doubt I was really a ninja?
Flower Shuriken!
Note: shinobi
Never popular with girls
but still an invincible ninja!
Raizo of the Mist is now...
...here before your eyes!
Raizo!
Nin! Nin!